

Jorge André Dias Silva

Computer Engineer

CONTACT Rua da Misericórdia nº332, Vila de Cucujães Oliveira de Azeméis, Aveiro, 3720-766 915 291 233 in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jorge16silva **SKILLS** ASP.NET Android AngularJS CSS C# Git Java/J2EE **JavaScript** Ionic Kotlin MySQL Python React.js REST TypeScript **PERSONAL QUALITIES** Communication Team Work Creativity Organization Pontuality Proativity Humor LANGUAGES -Portuguese English

ABOUT-

I'm a machine that transforms coffee into code with 22 years old, who lives in the area of Aveiro, specifically in Vila de Cucujães, graduated in Computer Engineering, with interest in new technologies and new programming languages. I am a person who likes challenges, to learn, to help, to work in teams, to investigate and takes advantage of all the experiences in which is involved.

EDUCATION -

Master's Degree in Computer Engineering, Software Engineering Branch Faculty of Sciences and Technology of the University of Coimbra 2017 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering, branch of application development

Coimbra Institute of Engineering (ISEC) | Coimbra 2014 - 2017

Science and technology course

Agrupamento de Escolas Serafim Leite | São João da Madeira 2010 - 2014

EXPERIENCE

Intern

Bluetrend Technologies | Coimbra February, 2017 - July, 2017

Development of an Android application for the payment management of services, involving Smart Card and NFC technology.

Intern

CISUC | Coimbra September, 2018 - July, 2019

Development of a hybrid platform for the NanoSen-AQM project through lonic technology.

VOLUNTEERING -

Math Tutor

CASPAE | Coimbra
October, 2015 – February, 2016 (5 months)
Mathematics Tutoring for ISEC Bachelors.

Assistant teacher

CASPAE | Coimbra

September, 2016 - December, 2017 (1 year and 4 months)

Assistant teacher, in the education of children of the 1st Cycle for Technology.

HOBBIES

French



Football





programming

languages





Run





Drink Coffee